<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DepthMapping</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Getting a depth map</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="take_picture">Take a photo</string>

    <string name="neiro_net">Neural network</string>
    <string name="instruction">Instruction</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="text_test">We present a standalone implementation of our merge operator. This new repository allows us to use any pair of monocular depth estimates in our double estimate. This includes using separate networks to evaluate basic and high resolution, using networks not supported by this repository (for example, Midas-v3), or using manually edited depth maps for artistic use. It will also be useful for scientists developing CNN-based MDE as a way to quickly apply double-evaluation to their own network. For more information, please take a look here. Use --max_res as an input argument for run.py combined with --Final to set a limit on the resolution of the results generated by our method.

We provide this parameter as a compromise between runtime and resolution. Using this reduces the execution time if only a result up to a certain megapixel is required.

This parameter sets a limit on the larger size of the result in pixels (while maintaining the proportions). For example, to generate results with a large size up to 2000 pixels, use the following:</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="detective_objects">Detected objects</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="segmentation">Segmentation</string>
    <string name="recognized_object">object recognition</string>
    <string name="depth_map">depth map</string>
    <string name="type_neironet">Type of neural network</string>
    <string name="secmentation_hint">Select the segmentation dimension. The dimension of segmentation will affect the quality of processing. The more segmentation, the better the quality.</string>
    <string name="origin">original</string>
    <string name="theme">theme</string>
    <string name="language">language</string>
    <string name="night_theme">dark</string>
    <string name="light_theme">light</string>
    <string name="instraction_header">INSTRUCTION</string>
    <string name="upload_image">upload image</string>
</resources>